<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Khoi Nguyen | Khoi Nguyen&#39;s Wesbite</title>
    <link>/author/khoi-nguyen/</link>
      <atom:link href="/author/khoi-nguyen/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Khoi Nguyen</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language>
    <image>
      <url>/images/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Khoi Nguyen</title>
      <link>/author/khoi-nguyen/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Khoi Nguyen</title>
      <link>/author/khoi-nguyen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/author/khoi-nguyen/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Khoi Nguyen is a PhD in Computer Science graduating from Oregon State University. His research interests include computer vision and machine learning. His primary research includes 2D/3D understanding, encompassing areas such as detection, segmentation, and reconstruction. In addition, he also explores the realms of Few-shot Learning and Vision-Language Models. Furthermore, Khoi is actively involved in advancing 2D/3D Generation, particularly in Efficient and Trustworthy Generative AI, contributing to push the boundaries of knowledge and innovation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Khoi Nguyen</title>
      <link>/author/khoi-nguyen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/author/khoi-nguyen/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Khoi Nguyen is a PhD in Computer Science graduating from Oregon State University advised by Professor Sinisa Todorovic. His primary research focuses on generative models, particularly diffusion and autoregressive models for visual content synthesis. He is also actively involved in advancing 2D and 3D understanding, including areas such as reconstruction, detection, and segmentation. Additionally, Khoi is passionate about few-shot, zero-shot learning, open-vocabulary learning, and vision-language models. He has published over many papers in top-tier Computer Vision conferences, including CVPR, ICCV, ECCV, and NeurIPS. His contributions extend beyond research, serving as a reviewer and Area Chair for prestigious conferences and journals like CVPR, ICCV, ECCV, ICLR, NeurIPS, and TPAMI. He earned the Outstanding Reviewer Award at ECCV 2020, and his team received the Best Paper - Honorable Mention Award at WACV 2023. At VinAI, Khoi leads the GenAI research theme, showcasing his leadership in cutting-edge research.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
